<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to Planck Bridge on</title><link>https://planckbridge.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to Planck Bridge on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://planckbridge.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What I Learned About Finance Playing 10,000 Poker Tournaments</title><link>https://planckbridge.github.io/blog/spins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planckbridge.github.io/blog/spins/</guid><description>&lt;p>After playing 10,000 poker tournaments, I discovered how to turn random outcomes into consistent profits. In this article, I’ll illustrate key concepts in statistics, using Spin and Go poker tournaments as a practical example of how individuals can leverage statistics to their advantage. I’ll also explore the similarities between professional poker players and financial traders, highlighting how both use their understanding of statistics and human behavior to succeed in a world driven by randomness.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Stock Indexes Teach Us</title><link>https://planckbridge.github.io/blog/stock-indexes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planckbridge.github.io/blog/stock-indexes/</guid><description>&lt;p>A study, &lt;em>The Capitalism Distribution&lt;/em> by Eric Crittenden and Cole Wilcox, analyzed the performance of approximately 8,000 U.S. stocks between 1983 and 2006. Surprisingly, while the S&amp;amp;P 500 Total Return Index increased by +1796% during this period, the average annualized return of all stocks was -1.06%. How can a market index do well when the average return of all stocks is negative? This post explores the study’s implications and introduces momentum trading.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://planckbridge.github.io/tools/asset-analysis-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planckbridge.github.io/tools/asset-analysis-tool/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Asset Analysis App&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://asset-returns-analysis.streamlit.app/">Visit here&lt;/a>&lt;br>
This tool allows users to analyze and compare the returns of financial assets. All calculations are based on daily adjusted closing prices, fetched directly from Yahoo Finance using the yfinance API.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://planckbridge.github.io/tools/spins-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://planckbridge.github.io/tools/spins-tool/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Poker Tournaments Simulation Tool&lt;/strong>: &lt;a href="https://spins-simulation.streamlit.app/">Visit here&lt;/a>&lt;br>
I created a Monte Carlo simulation in Python that models Spin and Go tournaments using the same payout structure as real tournaments. The simulation derives a player’s probability of winning a game from their expected average chips won per game (Chip EV). For players who do not finish first, the model assumes equal probabilities of finishing second or third.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>